(Penny:)You might slip on a banana peel
and get me pregnant.
(Sheldon:)I must say,
I'm shocked by this betrayal.
(Leonard:)I didn't betray Penny.
(Sheldon:)Not Penny, me.
(Leonard:)How am I betraying you?
(Sheldon:)Elizabeth's my friend,
and you're playing with her.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I guess I did.
(Howard:)What the hell are you doing?
(Raj:)Relax, it's Nyquil.
(Leonard:)-You still have a cold?
-Maybe, but I don't care.
(Raj:)That's the great thing about Nyquil,
it's like 10 percent booze.
(Raj:)I call it the nighttime
sniffling, sneezing, coughing...
...so-you-can-talk-to-girls medicine.
(Leonard:)Are you having trouble sleeping?
Because, boy, I was up all night.
(Raj:)Did you get a cold too?
No, I was awake all night.
(Howard:)If you want, I can give you
some of my mom's sleeping pills.